<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MoFlow</string>
    <string name="about_info">MoFlow created by Alex Oh\n\nFor user 
    manual and support see www.wolfpup.com</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="logoTextA">MoFlow</string>
    <string name="logoTextB">Initiative Tracker</string>
    <string name="groupItemInitText">Init Bonus:</string>
    <string name="groupItemACText">Armor Class:</string>
    <string name="groupItemHPText">Max Hit Points:</string>
    <string name="testText">testVal</string>
    <string name="contentDescription1">icon image</string>
    <string name="saveToCatalog">Save to Catalog</string>
    <string name="catalogDialogAmt">How many?</string>
    
    <string name="menuAdd">Add</string>
    <string name="menuSub">Remove</string>
    <string name="menuWait">Wait List</string>
    <string name="menuGrave">Graveyard</string>
    <string name="menuInit">Initiative</string>
    
    <string name="nextInit">Next</string>
    <string name="prevInit">Previous</string>
    
    <string name="rounds">Round: </string>
    
    <string name="initItemInit">Init: </string>
    <string name="initItemHP">HP: </string>
    <string name="initItemHPDivide">/</string>
    <string name="initItemAC">AC: </string>
    <string name="initItemConditions">Conditions: </string>
    
    <string name="menu_moveUp">Move Up</string>
    <string name="menu_itemWait">Wait</string>
    <string name="menu_itemRemove">Remove</string>
    <string name="menu_moveDown">Move Down</string>
    
    <string name="contentDescription2">divider</string>
    
    <string name="plusSign">+</string>
    <string name="minusSign">-</string>
    
    <string name="initiativeLabel">Initiative </string>
    <string name="hitPointsLabel">Hit Points </string>
    <string name="armorClassLabel">Armor Class </string>
    
    <string name="man_pcHeader">PC Manager</string>
    <string name="man_encHeader">Encounter Manager</string>
    <string name="man_catalogHeader">Creature Catalog</string>
    <string name="man_initHeader">Initiative</string>
    
    <string name="man_pcHelp">
        You can use the player character manager to save your player\'s characters so that
        they can be easily inserted into initiative later on. You can form different parties
        and place PCs into those parties.\n\n
        
        To add a new party, tap on the "Create New Party" button. A dialog will appear where
        you can name your party. Once finished, your party name will appear in the list. To
        rename a party or to delete it, tap-hold the item until a menu appears. To add
        PCs into a party, just tap the name of the party to load the party screen.\n\n
        
        To add a PC into the party, tap the "Add PC" button. A dialog will appear where you
        can enter in character details. Your PCs must have unique names. When you are finished,
        the PC will appear in the list. To modify an existing character, simply tap the item
        you wish to modify. To delete an item, tap-hold the item you wish to delete until a 
        dialog appears.\n\n
    </string>
    
    <string name="man_encHelp">
        You can use the encounter manager to prepare encounters so that they can be easily
        inserted into initiative later on. You can form different encounters and place 
        monsters from the creature catalog into your encounters.\n\n
        
        To add a new encounter, tap on the "Create New Encounter" button. A dialog will appear where
        you can name your encounter. Once finished, your encounter name will appear in the list. To
        rename an encounter or to delete it, tap-hold the item until a menu appears. To add
        creatures into an encounter, just tap the name of the encounter to load the encounter screen.\n\n
        
        To add a creature into the encounter, tap the "Add Creature" button. A dialog will appear 
        showing you all the creatures that exist in the creature catalog. Tap a creature in the
        dialog to add it to the list. To modify an existing creature, simply tap the item you 
        wish to modify. To delete an item, tap-hold the item you wish to delete until a dialog appears.\n\n
    </string>
    
    <string name="man_catalogHelp">
        You can use the creature catalog to save the creatures that will appear in your adventures
        and campaigns. It is necessary to insert items into the creature catalog if you want to use the encounter
        manager, since the creature catalog is used to populate encounters.\n\n
        
        To add a new creature to the catalog, tap the "Add New Creature" button. A dialog will
        appear where you can enter in creature details. Once finished, the item will appear
        in the catalog list. To modify a creature, just tap on it. To delete a creature, tap-hold
        until a dialog appears.\n\n
    </string>
    
    <string name="man_initHelp">
        All initiative list options are accessed through your Android options key. When you hit the options
        key, you have the choice of "Add", "Remove", "Wait List", or "Initiative".\n\n
        
        The Add option allows you to add a new item, party, encounter, or a creature from the catalog to the list.\n\n
        
        The Remove option allows you to remove either only players, only monsters, or all items from the list.\n\n
        
        The Wait List option allows you to put back into the initiative those players or monsters who have decided
        to wait their turn. When players are reinserted back into the list, the players are inserted before the
        item that currently has initiative. An item can only be sent to the wait list if the item has initiative.\n\n
        
        The Initiative option allows you to restart initiative, sort the list in ascending or descending order, or
        automatically roll initiative for either only players, only monsters, or for everyone. Auto-rolling
        will sort the items in descending order.\n\n
        
        If you tap-hold an item, you can move that item up or down in the list, send it to the wait list (if it 
        has intiative), or remove the item. Moving the item up or down will not change it\'s initiative value,
        so if you wish to reset it, it must be done manually.\n\n
        
        To modify the initiative value, hit points, and armor class of an item, just tap the item and a dialog
        will appear where you can edit the values. Press the "OK" button to finish.\n\n
        
        To start initiative, add some items to the list and hit the next button.\n\n
    </string>
    
    <string name="credits">
        Wolf Pup Software\n
        Programming: Alex Oh\n
        Artwork: Alexander Forssberg\n
    </string>
</resources>
